The End
North latitude 28 degrees 24 minutes.
West longitude 80 degrees 36 minutes.
Go there, and wait patiently
for the next new moon.
That, my friend, is when heaven will come.
I have no further use for this prison.
The child that was born is
already in my possession.
Here's the story of Jailhouse Locke.
Try as you might, you can only
remember three things at a time.
I know I need something, but what?
What's important?
What's something I cannot forget?
I have something important to tell
Jolene. I gotta go. She needs me.
Wait a minute.
What the hell was I doing?
Hmm...
something...
isn't right.
Wait, what?
That doesn't make any sense.
Why would he go into that building?
I don't understand this show!
Just let it play!
Why do you always have to keep
on doing what you're doing?
Take the remote from her!
I don't know what the
fuck is happening anymore!
And drag her dumb ass out of here!
Huh?
Fine, I won't watch it then.
You happy now?
All right, newbie.
That there spider's the boss of this cell.
Oh, hey, good to meet you, man.
Hope we can get along.
They call me Ron the Viper.
Oh, uh, yeah, of course. Appreciate it.
And that spider over there
is on the brink of death.
Yo, sup, bro?
What is this?
How the hell is any of
this supposed to be funny?
Man, this comic book is a mess.
I don't get it at all.
Where am I? The rec room?
I must have had a good
reason to come in here.
Oh yeah, I have to go see Emporio.
I'm here to find another way to
break out of this place, somehow.
There's the medical wing.
Emporio's room is off that staircase.
It's usually a walk in the park,
but they beefed up security today.
So how do I get to Emporio in one piece?
Shit! It's a stand!
And I know I've seen it before! The enemy!
I've got to go after it!
And that woman's the user!
I'm going to be able to move on.
I'm going to be moving on.
I'm going to be a trap and a hate.
Okay, alright.
It's not a survival day.
Get away from.
Go, go, go.
I don't wanna fade.
Let's go, go.
1, 2, 3.
Come and find a way.
Break out,
don't stop beating,
I'm out.
Wait a second.
Where am I?
And who was I chasing after just now?
What is happening? I caught her!
We're at the corner of hallway D12.
You, hands up!
Oh no!
The one being chased right now is me!
Look! Here she comes! Hey! Don't move!
Huh?
I could have sworn there were
two guards there a second ago.
Who cares?
Doesn't matter right now.
What is this place?
Seriously, how did I even get here?
Why are they all after me?
Where is she?
I know I saw her head that way!
Find her.
Go move your ass.
There's no way she just disappeared.
She's got to be hiding somewhere close by.
Maybe she ran toward the stairwell.
Not a chance.
She would have had to pass right by us.
We'd have seen her.
The stairwell?
Go see Emporio.
Okay, it's coming back to me.
Those are the stairs that
lead to Emporio's room.
What was I doing just now?
Oh yeah, I spilled the water
and it went everywhere.
There's something I need to tell Jolene.
I have to get to her before it's too late.
But I have to write somewhere
else before I forget it all again.
I need to make sure she sees the mugshot.
Or else I won't be able to tell her...
tell her that.
Jolene Kujo.
Since you can only retain up
to three memories at a time,
even if there are four
guards chasing after you,
you'll only be able to
remember three of them.
Of course your eyes will be able to see
all of them totaling more than four,
but your brain will outright
reject them as a memory
Go see Emporio.
I made you guide me here
Interesting who would have
thought I'd find a secret room
Emporio?
J-Jolene, when did you get here?
I just showed up.
Oh, look at your hand.
Poor you, what happened?
This looks awful.
Wait, is this because you can
only remember three things,
These two?
My arms have the exact
same writing on them!
Ever since being in solitary!
Oh yeah, I remember now!
I wanted to talk to you, Jolene!
There's something really
important I need to tell you!
Are you listening to me? Uh, what?
Sorry, what was I doing?
Hey wait, when did you get here,
Jolene? And why? Very funny.
Seriously, why am I here?
Why, why, why, why?!
Oh, that's right.
I came to see you and it's urgent.
But I have no idea why.
I just knew that if I didn't
come, I'd be up Schitt's Creek.
Print it out.
Yes, I've gotta print it out!
And fast, or else I'm
gonna forget it forever!
That's the only way I can save it!
Print what out, Emporio?
What do you mean when
you say print it out?
How do I, um, what was...
was it again?
Um, let's see...
Name, Miu Miu.
Rank, Chief Guard.
Oh, I get it.
So last time we met, that little
rat was there with you too.
He saw my face and my
stand, and he heard my name.
That Emporio was inside the
wall in the solitary cell.
Usually, I'd leave him alone.
My jailhouse lock's duty is to
spot who the stand users are,
track them down, and make
sure they're locked up.
But if there's any evidence of me
out there, that's another story.
So stand down, you jailbreaker!
Her stand, Stone Ocean, is too strong, so
these bullets will be useless against her.
But I know you won't remember this.
That if I had shot four bullets at you,
you would have no clue
where the last bullet went.
You'd piss your pants not knowing
whether it hit you or missed you.
He wouldn't even be able to see or smell
one wisp of smoke from the gunpowder.
J-Jolene.
What?
I don't know why there's a room
nor why there's a kid here.
The whole thing sure
smells suspicious as fuck.
Although Palesnake
mentions somebody in here.
Is in cahoots with Jolene,
scheming and coordinating elaborate escape
plans with walkie-talkies
and other technology.
He must have been talking about you.
And now all the data he collected is gone.
What a waste of time.
You rotten bitch, I'm gonna make you pay!
Huh, such passion.
Too bad, after these next three things,
even those fervent emotions will be
as lost as your chance at freedom.
That's the beauty of
what Jailhouse Lock does.
Eat shit, Jolene Cujo.
This is the end.
Out of this hail of bullets, you're
only gonna be aware of three.
The rest will pierce your
body like knives into butter!
You can try to fuck with my head all
you want, but the reflection won't lie.
No matter how many shots you fire at once,
I'm gonna see every single
one of them in the blood.
And I'm sure you haven't
forgotten anything, have you?
It's too late.
I've already destroyed the computer.
My only choice is to bail out.
What's the difference?
Jolene's going to forget me
in about two seconds anyway.
I'll be forgotten forever.
Not even a memory.
Emporio, try to hang on a little longer.
I'm going after that bitch.
I don't think you should, Jolene.
We both know.
You're...
you're gonna forget again the
minute you leave this room.
You're even gonna forget that
you'll have to defeat her.
So please...
Emporio, look.
I understand you wanting to be careful.
I like that about you.
How else were you gonna survive
this shit-bucket prison?
You needed to be that way.
But still,
eventually it's going to
get to the point where
you have to make a move
even if it's risky.
So you've got to understand.
For me, that time is now!
Is this Jolene's Thread?
I'm hurt.
How'd this happen to me?
But still,
eventually it's going to get to the
point Where you have to make a move,
even if it's risky.
I still don't know what it is.
But I know I'm supposed to do
something really important.
Something like...
That's right.
I have to print it out.
That's what I need to tell Jolene.
So I'll print it out and...
But what was it again?
What was the thing I'm supposed to print?
I don't even have a printer in my room.
So how can I...
It's so strong!
Yep, she's the enemy.
She's not going to get
away from me this time.
Come back, I need you!
I'm at the stairs at D10!
I see them!
They're right over there!
Chief Beauty was being attacked!
The gate! Open it! Hurry up!
Wait, where am I? What happened?
What am I doing here?
Move it!
Grab her before she escapes!
They're chasing someone!
It's me!
That's right, I called
the three guards back.
Now any and all memories you had of me
are lost forever, just like your freedom.
Oops.
Get up and run a bit, honey.
That'll give them more of a reason
to put a bullet in your head.
Oh right, those big strong arms.
I nearly forgot they can
deflect any shots at you.
My official sworn duty is really only
to make sure Stand users get put away.
But I'm rather excited you're
getting more than that.
Knowing you're about
to die makes me giddy.
If anyone deserves it, it's you.
This is all because you refuse to
behave and be a good little doggy.
I got her!
Oh, also, the fact that you can only
see three guards in front of you
is driving me wild with joy.
You're never getting past my jailhouse
lock, so you might as well stop fighting it!
Hey, Jolene, when did you get here?
I know you. You're Emporio!
Wait, Jolene, you gotta know.
This needs to be printed out, or else
I was gonna forget it in no time.
Print what out?
It's in binary code.
The language only uses ones and zeros.
I think I calculated it right.
You'd be able to print it out how
you'd be able to understand it.
What I'm saying is, you're the
printer who can memorize it!
Stone Ocean!
Binary is universal.
All things can be represented
with numeric sequencing.
If your thread can draw the
ones and zeros exactly right,
then Stone Ocean will become the printer?
that'll express it digitally.
Should I consider you to be the enemy?
Well, are you my enemy?
You've lost your mind.
There's no way you can see me.
Now, say your last goodbye.
Thanks for that.
You just confirmed it for me.
Because you are.
Holy shit!
What the hell am I seeing?
That psycho took Chief Miu Miu hostage!
Hey, Emporio.
I disabled Jailhouse
Lock's hold on you and me.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think I'm okay now.
Good.
Then I'm out.
Like I said before, I'm
breaking out of here.
What are you going to do?
If you insist on staying in this hole,
you'd better get back to your room.
Hey, Jolene.
I just realized now's my time.
I want to see the outside world.
Look!
There's a kid with her now?
Why is there a kid in this prison?
Focus, men!
Don't let your guard down!
All right, Emporio, you ready? Let's go.
Excuse me, you're in my way.
I'm coming through.
Sorry, thanks.
Please step aside, gentlemen.
Huh?
Who am I aiming at, then?
Hey, why am I in the hallway?
How did we all get here?
Thanks, Miu Miu. Nice job.
You catch on quick.
I almost like you. First,
we're going to head
straight to the medical wing
to treat the injuries
you caused to Emporium.
But I'm still counting on
your magic jailhouse, Locke.
I'm counting on that invincible
power, the power of three.
Where the hell am I?
You have Dad's disc, right?
Yeah, I've had it the whole time.
Jolene! That you?
Holy shit, it is you!
And Emporio 2!
Hey, Hermes!
I recognize the sound of that chaos.
I knew it had to be you guys.
Who's the carcass?
Actually, she's the chief
guard of this prison.
Huh?
Are you guys saying you're about to...
Yes, it's a prison break, and
we're about to leave any minute.
You're going after the priest, right?
You got it, Hermes.
Whatever that thing was he got his
hands on, I'm gonna go seal it.
I'm seeing this thing through.
I've never been more resolved than this.
Then I think you gotta take me with you.
Oh, my God.
Thank you, Father.
How fortunate you were here.
I'm sorry to ask, but are you unwell?
No, dear.
I'm just a bit fatigued, that's all.
Goodness, are you sure you're okay?
Excuse me.
Oh my god, what is happening here?
What the hell is wrong with these eggs?
My stand i haven't the
vaguest idea what it
is but it's painfully
clear that it's no longer
Pale snake what is it what could it be i
feel terrible something
is quickly raging out
of Control inside of me there's some kind
of independent power
that's ignoring my will
But oddly i feel hope
in this power hope in
fact is the one and only
thing i feel from it?
Dio's note recorded in Jotro's memories.
Perhaps that is what I need
to control this power, then.
The time and place.
North latitude 28 degrees, 24 minutes.
West longitude 80 degrees, 36 minutes.
Delightful.
Heaven appears to be there after all.
And that place is at Cape Canaveral.
Kennedy Space Center, to be precise.
The time is the new
moon, six days from now.
Of some place.
Other than he.
Although you think I smile.
Inside and all the while.
I'm wondering.
About my destiny?
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming far away.
From today!
Thank you.